[音乐
[MUSIC]
]我想讨论为什么编程语言课程实际上是在Coursera，三个
I want to discuss why the Programming Languages course is actually on Coursera,
疗程的A部分，B部分，C部分，为什么我们做出这一决定，
three courses Part A, Part B, Part C, why we made that decision and
并三块如何结合在一起的。
how the three pieces fit together.
因此，我们把它分成三个部分最大的原因是因为它是一个
So the biggest reason we split it into three parts is because it's a large
大的过程中，有大量的材料。
course, there's a lot of material.
谁已经完成了整个过程，部分A，B和Part C，人们
People who've finished the entire course, Part A, Part B and Part C,
100〜200小时左右的地方度过的。
have spent somewhere between 100 and 200 hours.
这很大程度上取决于人的速度有多快，他们经过材料。
It very much depends on the person and how quickly they go through the material.
所以它只是好像很多，一路上最现代化的课程，
And so it just seemed like a lot, the way most modern courses,
在线课程，在这一点上呼吁所有的一门课程。
online courses are at this point to call that all one course.
这是什么，对应于一些学生在我的大学做
This is something that corresponds to something that students in
在10或11周的
my university do over a 10 or
时间，而他们并没有试图做很多其他的事情在他们的生活，
11 week period while they're not trying to do a lot of other things in their lives,
虽然他们是在同时服用其他几个课程。
although they are taking a couple other courses at the same time.
现在，拆分起来是不容易的，我做的。
Now splitting it up was not easy for me to do.
如果你能想像写一本小说，然后有一个
If you can imagine writing a novel and then having someone say,
人说，我真的只是想读前几章。
I really only want to read the first few chapters.
这是一种我觉得怎么分手了课程。
That's kind of how I feel splitting up the course.
它确实都结合在一起，
It really does all fit together,
也有交叉的主题，只有真正弄懂，一旦你到达终点。
there are cross-cutting themes that only really make sense once you get to the end.
还有，一旦你得到那个绑在一起巧妙的事情分为B和Part C.
There are neat things that tie together once you get into Part B and Part C.
有对比，我们不能做，直到在病程晚期。
There are contrasts that we can't do until late in the course.
而总体而言，我已经投入了很多心思的是在这个过程
And overall, I've put a lot of thought into what is in this course and
中同样重要的，什么不是，就什么都有了某种打包为一个
just as importantly, what is not, to have it all sort of packaged up as one
整体，告诉一致的故事，从开始到结束的。
piece that tells a consistent story from beginning to end.
我不能强调不够，我是多么希望你们所有人参加所有的
And I cannot emphasize enough how much I want all of you to participate all
方式，通过对部分C的结束
the way through to the end of Part C.
而且，事实上，这里的目的不是将其分为三个课程，
And, indeed, the goal here was not to split it into three courses that try to
尽量让更
make more money or
多的钱，或让你觉得你做的三倍多，你实际上做。
make you think you're doing three times more than you're actually doing.
通常，当我说的过程中，我的意思是一切。
And usually, when I say the course, I mean everything.
所以我在这里所做的基本上是认为我不应该分裂它，但显然我们
So what I've done here is basically argue that I shouldn't have split it up,
没有，所以现在让我解释一下为什么我们做的原因。
but obviously we did, so let me now explain the reasons why we did.
最大的一个是，有更多的只是物质和它的更具挑战性，
The biggest one is that there's just more material and it's more challenging and
你在某种意义上应得的信贷完成三个疗程的材料价值，
you in some sense deserve the credit for completing three courses worth of material
而且我们把它分解的地方是合理的中间里程碑。
and the places where we split it are reasonable intermediate milestones.
他们的地方，你应该感到很自豪越来越远的，
They are places where you should feel very proud of getting that far and
如果你选择不走的更远，你会学到一些东西，
if you choose to go no further, you will have learned something and
它们的排序是合理的停靠站，使意义。
they sort of are reasonable stopping points that make sense.
所以，你应该承认为，它的东西，当我们有一切融合在一起，
So you deserve recognition for that, it's something that when we had
因为我们没有，当我们第一次提出这个MOOC，我们没有这个。
everything together, as we did when we first offered this MOOC, we didn't have.
因此，我认为这是在一个非常好的方向迈出的一大步。
And so I think that's a great step in a really good direction.
它也会给你一个机会休息一下，如果你愿意。
It will also give you a chance to take a break, if you will.
当你经过一个部分，你真的不想失去势头。
As you go through Part A, you really don't want to lose momentum.
你想要做的每件作品中那种连续两周的课程，
You want to do each piece of the course in sort of consecutive weeks, so
让你可以跟踪一切。
that you can keep track of everything.
但是，如果你想开始部分B.起飞前几个星期或一个月关闭
But if you wanted to take a couple weeks off or a month off before starting Part B.
那么，它可能是一个有点艰难记得你在哪里，
Well, it might be a little tough to remember where you were and
并再次上手，但同样的，因为它是一个合理的停车点，
get started again but, again, because it's a reasonable stopping point,
我倒认为这使得有很大的意义。
I actually think that makes a lot of sense.
因此，这是一种方式一种是让你通过整个课程以较慢
And so it's a way that kind of let you go through the overall course at
的速度，通过按一定的速度为A部分去排序，
a slower pace by going sort of at a certain pace for Part A and
然后采取B部分之前休息之类的事情。
then taking a break before Part B that sort of thing.
所以它是如何分解的术语，我说不幸的
So in terms of how it breaks down, I say unfortunately,
是，该课程的每个部分在不同的编程语言来完成。
each part of the course is done in a different programming language.
我说不幸，因为它反馈到这种想法，课程
I say unfortunate because it feeds back into this idea that the parts of
的部分是哪里我一直在强调，他们是真的不语言。
courses are about the languages where I keep emphasizing that they're really not.
但无论如何，这是事情是如何打破。
But nonetheless, that is how things break down.
我还要强调的是，我们并没有打破它投入三分，对不对？
I should also emphasize that we didn't break it into thirds, right?
我们选择了合理的停靠站，并制定出的方法
We picked the reasonable stopping points, and the way that worked out
是B部分绝对是三个部分的最大部分。
is Part B is definitely the biggest part of the three parts.
而且我们可以把一个部分成两个较小的碎片，也许我们可以，
And could we divide Part A into two smaller pieces, maybe we could but
但我没有看到一个自然的突破点，所以我没有，没事吧？
I don't see a natural breaking point, so I didn't, all right?
因此，这打破了办法是，A部分有三个家庭作业，
So the way this breaks down is that Part A has three homework assignments and
然后有没有家庭作业，但确实有考试第四
then a fourth substantial section that has no homework assignment but
实体部，所以完成A部分，是当然的真正四大单元。
does have an exam, so to finish Part A, is really four major units of the course.
然后，B部分只有两个单位，所以对A部分的一半大小，
Then Part B is only two more units, so about half the size of Part A, although,
但是，这些单位的第二个有什么通常被认为在使用过程中
the second of those units has what's usually considered the most challenging,
最具挑战性，也是最有价值的功课。
and also most rewarding homework in the course.
然后，C部分，在那里我们学习面向对象编程，然后比较，
And then Part C, where we study object oriented programming and then compare and
并与我们在A部分和B部分做函数式编程对比回来，
contrast it back with the functional programming that we do in Part A and
刚刚另外两个家庭作业，但再一次期末考试。
Part B, has just another two homeworks but then a final exam.
这考试主要集中在零部件B和C.
And that exam focuses mostly on Parts B and C.
因为你会发现B部分没有考试。
because you'll notice Part B doesn't have an exam.
而是指一点点与零件对比，因为当你到课程结束，
But refers a little bit to contrast with Part A, because when you get to the end of
你会看到，这是应该做适当的事情。
the course you'll see that that's an appropriate thing to do.
这么干脆，东西都在三个部分一个疗程。
So altogether, things are one course in three parts.
我希望你明白，。
I hope you appreciate that.
这也许很明显，但我会说出来，你不能真正做到B部分没有一个
It's perhaps obvious, but I'll say it, that you can't really do Part B without
部分，你不能真正做到C部分没有A部分和
Part A and you can't really do Part C without Parts A and
B部分，因为他们往往是指回前面的部分。
Part B because they often refer back to earlier parts.
这就是我们如何划分的事情了这个
And that's the story of how we divided things up and
故事，我们希望您充分利用你现有的材料，
we hope that you make the most of the material available to you
以最有意义到你的方式。
in the way that makes the most sense to you.